A Wounded Fawn is a horror film directed by Travis Stevens.
A local museum curator who is dipping her toe back into the
dating pool is targeted by a charming serial killer.
When a fateful romantic getaway between the two becomes a tense game of
cat and mouse, both must confront the madness within him.
Bruce Ernst, played by Josh Ruben.
Meredith Tanning, played by Sarah Lind.
Kate Horna, played by Malin Barr.
Leonora, played by Katie Kuang.
Wendy, played by Tanya Everett.
Julia, played by Laksmi Hedemark.
A Wounded Fawn is a 2022 American horror film directed by Travis
Stevens and written by Stevens and Nathan Faudree.
It stars Sarah Lind, Josh Ruben and Malin Barr.
The film explores themes of date, surrealism, serial killer, art.
The tone is dark and mind_bending and intense.